Marat Saitov

Russia, Orenburg +79058903936

E-mail: marat4568731@gmail.com GitHub: github.com/JoeMattew

In my journey as a developer, I have immersed myself in a diverse set of technologies and tools, including HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, React, and Node.js. Over the past year, I have dedicated myself to mastering these technologies and honing my skills in web development. I find great joy in writing code because it allows me to bring ideas to life and create meaningful and interactive experiences for users. The process of problem-solving, designing elegant solutions, and continuously learning and improving my skills is what fuels my passion for coding.

Education

High School (1998-2003)
(International Certificate)
Course of the English language-600
Course of the Turkish language-315

Faculty of Economy and Administration Orenburg State University Foreign Economic Activity (2003-2008)

> Faculty of Law Orenburg State University Civil Law (2011-2013)

Languages

- 1. Russian(native)
- 2. English (advanced)
- 3. Turkish(pre-advanced)
 - 4. Chinese (beginner)

Professional Experience

Share School (Shenzhen, China)
2019-2021
English teacher
Groups of 8-10 students age 3-15

Readerland School (Shenzhen, China)
2018-2019
English teacher
Groups of 8-10 students age 3-9

Private English Tutor (Russia, Orenburg)
2017-2018
English teacher
Students age 7-18

Winner English School (Fuzhou, China)
2016-2017
English teacher
Groups of 8-10 students age 3-18

Private English Tutor (Russia, Orenburg) 2016-2009 English teacher Students age 7-18

Russian State DEA (Drug Enforcement Agency) 2010-2015 Policeman Control and monitor the work of the medical centers in use of medical preparations

USA Raleigh NC EVOO restaurant (tel 919-782-3866) 2007 Manager assistant

USA Cary NC Volvo of Cary 2006 Car Salesman

Qualification Profile

Extensive experience in different spheres. Very interested in philology and pedagogical disciplines. Exceptional leadership activities concerning team initiatives. Ability to improve and leverage skills and capabilities to participate in different kinds of activities. Outstanding interpersonal, motivational and presentation skills. Analytical, articulate and diligent.